<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<?xml-model href="http://www.tei-c.org/release/xml/tei/custom/schema/relaxng/tei_all.rng" type="application/xml" schematypens="http://relaxng.org/ns/structure/1.0"?>
<?xml-model href="http://www.tei-c.org/release/xml/tei/custom/schema/relaxng/tei_all.rng" type="application/xml"
	schematypens="http://purl.oclc.org/dsdl/schematron"?>
<TEI xmlns="http://www.tei-c.org/ns/1.0">
  <teiHeader>
      <fileDesc>
         <titleStmt>
            <title>Title</title>
         </titleStmt>
         <publicationStmt>
            <p>Publication Information</p>
         </publicationStmt>
         <sourceDesc>
            <p>Information about the source</p>
         </sourceDesc>
      </fileDesc>
  </teiHeader>
  <text>
      <body>
         <div type="head">
            <p><persName>MR. CHARLES EYTON</persName>
               Gen. Mgr. Famous Players-Lasky
               Statement taken <date>11-30-25</date> at 2:20 PM
            </p>
         </div>
         
         <div type="interview">
            <p>EYTON: (Speaking of the morning following the murder) I was called on the telephone, I should judge at 8 by his assistant Harry Fellows, and he told me. He said, "Mr. Eyton, when I came over to <placeName><persName>Mr. Taylor</persName>'s room</placeName> this morning, I found him dead." And I says, "Dead? What is the matter?" He says "Well, we have had a doctor here and he tells us it is a hemorrhage of the stomach. 
               
               That would make it about 8:30, I should judge.
               
               I didn't go through the house. <persName>Charley Maigne</persName> and Arthur Hoyt and Douglas MacLean and Harry Fellows [did].
               
               Douglas MacLean was the first man that put it into my head that he (Taylor) was murdered. He said he was confident that he had heard a shot the night before. He said to me, "Charley, don't let them take his body away without turning it over, because I think we heard a shot last night."
               
               POLICE: Have you any idea who did the telephoning around about the murder?
               
               EYTON: No. Harry Fellows telephoned me.
               
               POLICE: Did you hear anybody call up Mabel Normand or Mrs. Shelby?
               
               EYTON: No. That all happened before I got there, if Mrs. Shelby was called up. Mabel Normand was called up, I know. Charley Maigne told me.
               
               POLICE: What was the position of the body when you first saw it?
               
               EYTON: The body when I first saw it lay right in front of the desk, with the head back. The desk was near his feet.
               
               [GAP IN INTERVIEW] Of course Mary was engaged to marry Mickey Neilan, so she told me, but I don't think there was very much to that.
               
               POLICE: This trouble with Taylor, when was that?
               
               EYTON: He and Mickey? Oh, Mickey said something one night. They were drunk and Mickey apologized. It was nothing serious.
               
               POLICE: Do you know Neva Gerber?
               
               EYTON: Yes. That was one of Taylor's former flames, before any of this came up. When he went to war it was understood that when he came back he was going to marry Neva Gerber.
               
            </p>
         </div>
         
         
         
         
         
         
         
         
         
      </body>
  </text>
</TEI>
